https://www.suvinowineryaz.com/terms/

Welcome!
Terms of Service
Welcome to the Internet sites of Su Vino Winery Scottsdale, Inc. ("SuVinoWineryAZ.com"). SuVinoWineryAZ.com Site is operated by Su Vino Winery Scottsdale, Inc.and its affiliates (collectively referred to herein as "we," "us," or "our").
PLEASE NOTE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE IS SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING TERMS ("TERMS OF SERVICE"). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, DO NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THIS SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIALS CONTAINED ON THE SITE. YOUR USE OF THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE SHALL BE DEEMED TO BE YOUR AGREEMENT TO ABIDE BY EACH OF THE TERMS SET FORTH BELOW. THE TERMS OF SERVICE MAY BE UPDATED BY SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM FROM TIME TO TIME WITH OR WITHOUT NOTICE TO YOU. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE INDICATES ACCEPTANCE OF ANY MODIFICATIONS TO THE TERMS OF SERVICE.
[back to top]
User Obligations
You agree not to do any of the following while using the SuVinoWineryAZ.com Site:
Intentionally or unintentionally violate any applicable law or regulation.
Access, tamper with, or use nonpublic areas of the SuVinoWineryAZ.com Site or SuVinoWineryAZ.com's computer systems. Unauthorized individuals attempting to access or tamper with these areas may be subject to prosecution.
Frame or link to the SuVinoWineryAZ.com Site except as permitted in writing by SuVinoWineryAZ.com.
[back to top]
The Sale of Alcoholic Beverages
SuVinoWineryAZ.com does not sell alcohol to persons under the age of 21. When purchasing wine on this site you swear and affirm that you are over the age of 21. SuVinoWineryAZ.com makes every effort to ensure that alcoholic beverages are not delivered to anyone who is under the age of 21. By using this site you are acknowledging that the person receiving a shipment of alcoholic beverages from SuVinoWineryAZ.com is over the age of 21. You also agree that any alcohol purchased from SuVinoWineryAZ.com is intended for personal consumption and not for resale. If you do not agree with these conditions of use please do not use this site. If you intentionally or unintentionally misrepresent your age in order to provide alcohol to a person under the age of 21 SuVinoWineryAZ.com will prosecute you fully to the extent allowable by law.
[back to top]
Parental Control Protections
As required by the Communications Decency Act of 1996, SuVinoWineryAZ.com hereby notifies you that parental control protections (such as computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist you in limiting access to Content that may be harmful to minors. Among the many companies that provide Internet blocking and screening software are CyberPatrol, NetNanny, SurfWatch, and GuardOne. SuVinoWineryAZ.com does not sponsor or endorse any of these companies or their services.
[back to top]
Links
The SuVinoWineryAZ.com Site may contain links to other web sites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that SuVinoWineryAZ.com is not responsible or liable for (1) the availability or accuracy of such web sites or resources; or (2) the content, advertising, or products on or available from such web sites or resources. The inclusion of any link on the SuVinoWineryAZ.com Site does not imply that SuVinoWineryAZ.com endorses the linked site.
[back to top]
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE, THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE, THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY EVENTS, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES.
IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM SITE. THIS SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS SEPARATE AND INDEPENDENT OF ANY OTHER PROVISION THAT LIMITS SUVINOWINERYAZ.COM'S LIABILITY OR YOUR REMEDIES.
[back to top]
PRIVACY STATEMENT
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To quickly process your transactions.
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect your information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
We do not use cookies for tracking purposes
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.
However, you will still be able to place orders .
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal information:
• By emailing us
• By calling us
• By logging in to your account
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify you via email
• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
Su Vino Winery
7035 E. Main Street, Suite 110
Scottsdale, AZ 85251
info@suvinowineryaz.com
480-994-8466
[back to top]
The Terms of Service were updated November 10, 2016
Categories
Club Vino
Kegged Wines
Special Events / Classes
Wines for Charities
Wine Gift Baskets
Gift Certificates
Georgia - Bulldogs
Georgia "Bulldog"
Georgia "G"
Georgia Southern University - Eagles
Georgia Tech - Yellow Jackets
Georgia Tech "GT"
Georgia Tech "Yellow Jackets"
Illinois - Fighting Illini
Iowa State - Cyclones
Iowa State "I"
Kansas - Jayhawks
Kansas State - Wildcats
Kennesaw State - Owls
Kentucky - Wildcats
Kentucky "UK"
Kentucky "Wildcats"
Louisiana at Lafayette - Ragin' Cajuns
Louisiana State University - Tigers
Louisville - Cardinals
Marshall University - Thundering Herd
Maryland - Terrapins
Memphis - Tigers
Miami - Hurricanes
Michigan State University - Spartans
Middle Tennessee State University - Blue Raiders
Mississippi - Ole Miss
Mississippi State University - Bulldogs
Mississippi State "Bulldogs"
Mississippi State "M"
Missouri - Tigers
Navy - United States Naval Academy
Naval Academy "Bill the Goat"
Naval Academy "Crest"
Nebraska - Cornhuskers
Nevada - Wolf Pack
New Mexico - Lobos
North Carolina State University - Wolf Pack
NC State "NCS"
Ohio State - Buckeyes
Oklahoma - Sooners
Oklahoma State University - Cowboys
Oregon State - Beavers
Purdue - Boilermakers
South Carolina - Gamecocks
South Carolina "Gamecocks"
South Carolina "SC"
Southern Miss - Golden Eagles
Stephen F. Austin - Lumberjacks
Tennessee - Volunteers
Texas A&M - Aggies
Texas Christian University - Horned Frogs
Texas Tech - Red Raiders
Utah - Utes
West Texas A&M - Buffaloes
Virginia - Cavaliers
Virginia Military Institute - Keydets
Virginia Tech - Hokies
Virginia Tech "Hokies"
Virginia Tech "VT"
Washington State University - Cougars
West Virginia - Mountaineers
Vanderbilt - Commodores
Wake Forest - Demon Deacons
Wake Forest "Demon Deacons"
Wake Forest "WF"
Western Kentucky - Hilltoppers
2019 CFP National Champions Louisiana State University
Military & Civil Servants Accessories
Air Force
Air Force Academy
Air Force
Army
U.S. Military Academy - West Point
Review Us On
Home | Contact Us | Shipping Policy | Blog | Site Map | Terms & Conditions | Copyright © 2015. All Rights Reserved. 7330 E. Main St., Suite 105 Scottsdale,AZ 85251 7330 E. Main Street, Suite 105  •
Scottsdale, AZ 85251
© 2007 - 2020 suvinowineryaz.com . All Rights Reserved.
